Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  - Nature
    Neumann, Edel Agathe
    Maddox, John
    Fisher, Knight & Co., Ltd.
    Brimble, Lionel John Farnham
  - "Nature and the Doctor"
    Allen, Chester D
    Boyers, L M
    Cohn, Arnold E
    Elwood, Everett S
    Elliott, Jabez H
    Fitz, Reginald
    Furstenberg, A C
    Greenwald, Isidor
    JAMA
    Leake, Chauncey D
    MacNider, William DeB
    McDermott, Frank A
    Needham, J G
    Rosenau, Milton J
    Staniland, Julia L
    Stockard, C R
    Walker, R H
    West, Randolph
    Trask, James D
  - Nauts, Mrs. Helen Coley
  - Neill, H M
  - Nelson, Dorothy
  - Nettleship, Anderson
  - Neuberger, A
  - New Willard Hotel
  - New York Academy of Medicine
    Wood, Francis Carter
    Sachs, Bernard
    Williams, Linsly R
    Craig, Howard Reid
    Cannan, R K
    Palmer, Walter W
    Galdston, Iago
    Malloch, Archibald
    Martland, Harrison S
    Ashford, Mahlon
    Woodruff, I Ogden
    Labalme, George
    Cole, Rufus I
    Hartwell, John A
    Kennedy, Foster
    Reynolds, Frederick P
    Goodridge, Malcolm
    Miller, James Alexander
    Lydenberg, Harry M
    Rice, Paul North
    Rider, Fremont
    Keogh, Andrew
    Brewster, James
    Williamson, C C
    Corwin, H L
    Annan, Gertrude
    Hellman, Eva
    Cranefeld, Paul F
  - New York Academy of Sciences
    Miner, Eunice Thomas
    Tsutsui, Minoru
  - New York Board of Fire Underwriters
  - New York Central RR
  - New York City - Bureau of Nuisances
  - New York Herald Tribune
    Grant, Lester
  - New York Hospital
    Diethelm, Oskar
  - New York Institute of Clinical Oral
    Pathology
    Cahn, Lester, R
    Roistacher, G
    Blum, Theodor
    Levy, Bernard
    DuBos, Rene Jules
  - New York Live Poultry Commission
    Merchant's Ass'n, Inc.
    Dwyer, E V
  - New York Pathological Society
    Paige, Beryl H
    Zimmerman, H M
    Wood, Francis C
    Clarke, B Earl
    Berkman, James I
  - New York Physical Therapy Society
    McGuinness, Madge C L
  - New York Post
  - New York Public Library
    Wilson, Eunice Comstock
  - New York Railways Co.
  - New York Society Library
    Bigelow, Frank B
  - New York State College of
    Forestry
  - New York State Income Tax Bureau
  - New York Telephone Co.
  - New York Times
    Campion, T B
    Sullivan, Walter
    Graves, C M
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association
  - New York Zoological Society
  - Newburgh, L H
  - Newspaper Clippings
  - Newton, Grant
  - Nichols, Roger W
  - Nigg, Clara
  - Nightingale, Michael
    Wragg, Peter
  - Nishihara, Gentaro
  - Nissen, Beatrice
  - Nissen, Rudolf
  - Alfred Nobel and the Nobel Prizes
    Klein, George
  - Nobel Prize -- Congratulatory letters, 1966
    VIEW COMPLETE LISTING OF LETTERS
  - Nobel Prize, Bernhard, C. G.
    - Acceptance Speech
  - Nobel Prize, "Crank" Letters
    - Corbiere, H
    - Manna, Gino DeL
    - George, Abraham
    - Ja
  - Nobel Prize - Newsclippings
  - Nobel Prize, Printed Items
  - Nobel Prize - Requests for Aid Against Cancer
  - Nobel Prize - Acceptance Speech
  - Nobel Prize, Rous. Address to the University Students, 1966 Dec. 10.
  - Nobel Prize, Rous. Challenge to Man of the Neoplastic Cell
  - Noble, K. G.
  - Noice, Frank
  - Noguchi, Hideyo
    - Hutchison, Mary
    - Takahashi, Akira
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Plesset, Isabel R
  - Norman, F
  - Norske Videnskaps-Akademi Oslo
    - Bull, Francis
    - Amundsen, Leiv
  - Northrop, John H
  - Norton, Warder W
  - Norton, W.W., & Co.
    - Lunt, Storer B
    - Brockway, George P
  - Noyes, Wilbur F
  - Nuese, Robert
  - Nukada, Susumu
  - Nye, Robert N
  - Oberling, Charles
    - Speech: "Persepctives in Virology"
    - Memoir by Dr. Rous
    - Powers, John H
    - MacKenzie, George
    - Haguenau, Francoise
  - Oberling, Charles. Memorial Volume
    - Bordley, James, III
    - DuShane, Graham
    - Lemaire, Andre
    - Haguenau, Francoise
  - Oberling, Marthe
  - Oberling, Pierre
  - Oberrender, Girard
  - O'Brien, Daniel P
  - O'Brien, R O
  - O'Connor, Basil
  - Odio De Granada, Gustavo
  - O'Donnell, John J
    - Hori, Ichiro E
  - O'Donnell, Walter E
  - Offutt, Dorsey K
  - Ogata, Tomosaburo
  - Ogonowski, W
  - Okuneff, N
    - Pearce, Richard M
  - Olcott, Charles T
  - Old, Lloyd, J
  - Old Hickory Bookshop
  - Olitsky, Peter K
  - Olive, J E
  - Oliver, Jean
    - Fremont-Smith, Frank
    - Greene, Roger S
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Hayes, J J
    - Pearce, John M
  - Oliver, Jean "The Gold Headed Cane"
    - Orville, J Lowell
    - Kinney
    - Fitzgerald, Patrick J
    - Graves, Mrs. Judy
  - Oliver, Wade W
  - Olms, James S
  - Olmstead, Hazel R
  - Olmstead, Rossiter D
  - Olsen, Kay
  - Olson, Carl, Jr.
  - Ophuls, William
  - Opie, Eugene L
    - Francis, Thomas, Jr.
    - Angevine, D Murray
    - West, Olin
    - Furth, Jacob
  - Opie, Eugene L Dinner (90th Birthday)
    - Century Association
    - Moore, Robert A
    - Dock, William
    - Kidd, John G
  - Oppenheimer, B S
  - Opthalmic Institute
  - Orbison, J Lowell
  - Orlando, Ruggiero
  - Orlinick, S
  - Orr, J W
  - Orr, Miss Martha
  - Osborn, Fairfield
  - Osborn, Herbert. Fund
  - Osgood, Wilfred H
  - Osler, William
    - McMurray, D
    - James, F Cyril
    - Matthews T H
    - Murray, E G D
    - Smith, Frederick
  - Osler Memorial Volume
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Abbott, Maude E
  - Osowitz, B M
  - Osserman, Freda
  - Osterhout, W J V
    - Zinsser, Hans
    - Swift, Homer F
    - Century Association
    - Bakewell, Charles M
    - Carrell, Alexis
    - Christian, Henry A
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Coolidge, Archibald C
    - Cushing, Harvey
    - Donaldson, Henry H
    - Ford, Worthington C
    - Fosdick, Raymond B
    - Gay, Edwin F
    - Greene, Jerome D
    - Hart, Albert B
    - Haskins, Charles H
    - James, Henry
    - Morgan, Thomas H
    - Kellogg, Vernon
    - Lowell, A Lawrence
    - MacDougal, D T
    - Merriam, John C
    - Paton, Stewart
  - Ottenberg, Reuben
  - Ottenheimer, Edward
  - Overman, John R
  - Owen, Margaret E
  - Pack, George T
  - Packchanian, A
  - Pagano, Matthew
  - Page, Irvine H
  - Page, J D
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Page, R E
  - Painter, Theophilus S
  - Palade, George E
  - Palmer, Catherine Gardella
    - Henderson, James S
  - Palmer, Walter Walker
  - Pantaleoni, Guido
  - Papparella, Vincenzo
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M
  - Paragon C & C Co.
  - Parfitt, Charles D
  - Park, Edwards A
  - Park, William H
  - Parker, Augustin H
  - Parker, Carey
  - Parker, F, Jr.
  - Parker, R R
  - Parker, Raymond C
  - Parnall, C G
  - Parran, Thomas
  - Parrott, Delphine M V
  - Parsons, Geoffrey
  - Parsons, L G S
  - Parsons, Robert J
    - Whitecotton. G Otis
  - Parsons, Talcott
  - Partington, Mrs. Helen
  - Pasadena Research Laboratories
    - Flinn, Waldo R
  - Passano, William M
  - Passey, R D
  - Pasteur Centenary
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Pautrier, I M
    - Gery, Louis
    - Roussy, G
  - Pathological Society of Great Britain and Ireland
  - Pathological Society of Philadelphia
    - McCutcheon, Morton
    - Ratcliffe, Herbert L
  - Pathology
    - Graves, Judy
  - Paton, R Townley
  - Patterson, Belknap & Webb
  - Patton, A R
  - Paul, John R
    - Andrewes, Christopher
  - Pauling, Linus
  - Paullin, James E
  - Payne, Fernandus
  - Peace Resolution
  - Peabody, Francis W
  - Peacock, P Michael
  - Peacock, Philip R
  - Pearce, Agnes M
  - Pearce, John Musser
  - Pearce, Louise
    - Kone, Eugene H
  - Pearce, Mary M
  - Pearce, Richard M
  - Pearse, Herman E
  - Pearson, Bjarne
  - Pearson, Fred
  - Peck, Mrs. E E Musgrave
  - Peise, James H.F.
  - Pentimalli, Francesco
    - Lambert, Robert A
    - Cramer, W
    - Murray, J A
    - Burchenal, Joseph H
  - Pentimalli, W
  - Percival, G H
  - Perkins, Maxwell Evarts
  - Perla, David
    - Marmorston-Gottesman, J
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Perry, Mrs. E B
  - Perspectives
    - MacLean, Kenneth
    - Ingle, Dwight J
    - Markham, Margaret
    - Pollard, Morris
    - Guideman, Sondra
    - Wood, Harrison F
    - Pollard, Morris
    - Landau, Mrs. Claire
    - Cooper, Henry S F
    - James, Henry
    - Hoeber, Paul B
    - Hinkel, Jo
  - Perspectives Symposium
  - Peter, Gustavo
  - Peterson, Harry
  - Peterson, Howard R
  - Petit, L
  - Petrzelka, Charles
    - Crutcher, Katherine G
  - Pfeiffer, Mildred C J
  - Phelps, Lillian A
  - Phi Kappa Psi
  - Phillips, Robert A
  - Phipps Institute (U. of Pa.)
  - Physiological Society of Great Britain
  - Pickens, E M
  - Pierce, Cynthia
  - Pilates, Joseph H
  - Pincus, Gregory
  - Pincus, Sol
  - Pink, Mrs. M
  - Pinkus, Hermann
  - Pirie, Antoinette
  - Pirone, Frank J
  - Plaut, Alfred
  - Plonskier, M
  - Poel, William E
  - Poffenberger, A T
  - Poker
  - Pollard, Morris
  - Pollia, Joseph A
  - Pollock, Richard A
  - Pomarico, John
    - Bader, George
  - Ponder, Eric
  - Ponder, Merle Hayes
  - Ponten, Jan
  - Poppensiek, George C
  - Population Crisis Committee
    - Draper, William H., Jr.
  - Porter, Keith R
    - Rogers, Stanfield
  - Post, Joseph
  - Potter, Paul
  - Poucher, Lynn
  - Powel, Lydia Bond
  - Powers, John H
  - Pratt, Arnold W
  - Prenzel, Mildred C
  - President's Conference on Heart Disease and Cancer
    - Sloan, Margaret H
    - Endicott, Kenneth M
    - Kennedy, John F
    - Jones, Boisfeuillet
  - Preu, Paul William
  - Prieto, Fernando E
  - Prince, Howard L
  - Prince, John E
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly
    - Smith, Edric B
    - Smith, Datus C
  - Principe, Eduardo
  - Proskauer, Joseph M
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
  - Prudden, Lillian E
  - Publication Department - Rockefeller Institute, 8 folders
    Primarily financial and administrative.
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 1)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 1)
    - Robertson, Albert D (Folder 1)
    - Gerard, Jean (Folder 1)
    - Cohen, Barnett (Folder 2)
    - Lorenz, A J (Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Florence (Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 3)
    - Gasser, Herbert S (Folder 3)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 4)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 4)
    - Gasser, Herbert S. (Folder 4)
    - Enders, John F (Folder 4)
    - Gortner, R. A. (Folder 4)
    - Hickerson, J. F. (Folder 4)
    - Rivers, Thomas M. (Folder 4)
    - Lester, A. M. (Folder 4)
    - Schmidt, Louis (Folder 4)
    - Stacy, J W., Inc. (Folder 4)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 5)
    - Flinn, W. R. (Folder 5)
    - Smith, Theobald (Folder 5)
    - Steward, Florence M. (Folder 5)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 6)
    - Flinn, Waldo R. (Folder 7)
    - Journal of Experimental Medicine (Folder 7)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 8)
    - Steward, Florence M. (Folder 8)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 8)
    - Robertson, H. D. (Folder 8)
  - Publication Department - Rockefeller Institute, Journal of Experimental Medicine, 42 folders
    - Archer, R. K. (Folder 1)
    - Draper, Estella (Folder 1)
    - Baxter, James H. (Folder 1)
    - Benacerraf, Baruj (Folder 1)
    - Benditt, Earl P (Folder 1)
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr. (Folder 1)
    - Broadbent, Margaret (Folder 1)
    - Campbell, Charles I. (Folder 1)
    - Stewart, Florence (Folder 1)
    - Holleman, W. Roy (Folder 2)
    - Chase, Merrill W. (Folder 2)
    - Cohen, Mrs. Barbara (Folder 2)
    - Coons, Albert H (Folder 2)
    - Dubos, Rene J. (Folder 2)
    - Cunliffe, Anthony C. (Folder 2)
    - Dumbell, Keith (Folder 3)
    - Eagle, Harry (Folder 3)
    - Ellis, John T. (Folder 3)
    - Engstrom, A. (Folder 3)
    - Finean, J. B. (Folder 3)
    - Farquhar, Marilyn G. (Folder 3)
    - Feldman, Joseph D. (Folder 3)
    - Finman, Judith (Folder 3)
    - Fittipoldi, J. J., Jr. (Folder 3)
    - Forenbacher, S. (Folder 3)
    - Friend, Charlotte (Folder 3)
    - Gilliatt, R. W. (Folder 3)
    - Griffiths, Raymond B. (Folder 3)
    - Hamilton, Susan D. (Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Thomas J. (Folder 3)
    - Hirst, George K. (Folder 3)
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr. (Folder 3)
    - Humphrey, J. H. (Folder 4)
    - Quintero Fossas, Jose (Folder 4)
    - Cohen, Barbara (Folder 4)
    - Jewett, Audrey (Folder 4)
    - Straus, Mrs. Ruth (Folder 4)
    - Kamran, Gwenyth (Folder 4)
    - Lathem, Willoughby (Folder 4)
    - Moat, Phyllis M. (Folder 4)
    - Dole, Vincent P. (Folder 4)
    - Lieberman, Melvin (Folder 4)
    - Gillet, Stanley A. (Folder 4)
    - Liu, Chien (Folder 4)
    - Boosey, Rosenagh (Folder 4)
    - McDermott, Walsh (Folder 4)
    - Linton, Mrs. Mabel (Folder 5)
    - Reis, Jose, Jr. (Folder 5)
    - Mellors, Robert C (Folder 5)
    - Metcoff, Jack (Folder 5)
    - Morgan, Councilman (Folder 5)
    - Morgan, Herbert R (Folder 5)
    - Obie, Alan (Folder 5)
    - Osowitz, B M (Folder 5)
    - Petescia, Joseph J (Folder 5)
    - Bloom, Grace (Folder 5)
    - Rees, T A (Folder 5)
    - Ribeiro, Luiz P (Folder 5)
    - Robertson, O H (Folder 5)
    - Rowe, Wallace P (Folder 6)
    - Ruch, T C (Folder 6)
    - Mink, S J (Folder 6)
    - Schubert, Herman J.P. (Folder 6)
    - Silver, D (Folder 6)
    - Skeggs, Leonard T (Folder 6)
    - Smith, Gertrude C (Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 6)
    - Tajima, Masanori (Folder 6)
    - Tal, Chloe (Folder 6)
    - Tsumita, Toru (Folder 6)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Beth (Folder 7)
    - Passano, William (Folder 7)
    - Weisberg, Sydney R (Folder 7)
    - Wheeler, Clayton E (Folder 7)
    - Whitaker, Douglas (Folder 7)
    - Wood, W Barry, Jr. (Folder 7)
    - Baird, Joan R (Folder 7)
    - Blunt, Blanche L (Folder 7)
    - Adelberg, Edward A (Folder 8)
    - Argyris, Thomas S (Folder 8)
    - Ruchton, Mrs. Marion L (Folder 8)
    - Askovitz, S I (Folder 8)
    - Babione, R W (Folder 8)
    - Bloch, Hubert (Folder 8)
    - Blunck, H (Folder 8)
    - Boyce, William H (Folder 8)
    - British Medical Bulletin (Folder 8)
    - Huggins, Charles B (Folder 8)
    - Broadbent, Margaret (Folder 8)
    - Burnett, George W (Folder 8)
    - Bustos, Anibal C (Folder 9)
    - Cheever, F S (Folder 9)
    - Rivers, J A (Folder 9)
    - Churchill, J. & A., Ltd. (Folder 9)
    - Chase, Beulah D (Folder 9)
    - Conklin, Groff (Folder 9)
    - Cook, J Gordon (Folder 9)
    - Coons, Albert H (Folder 9)
    - Rogers, Stanfield (Folder 9)
    - Cowen, P N (Folder 9)
    - Dannenberg, Arthur M., Jr. (Folder 9)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 9)
    - Whelan, Mary Ann (Folder 9)
    - Duggan, A J (Folder 10)
    - Dumbell, Keith (Folder 10)
    - Eaton, Monroe D (Folder 10)
    - Field, J W (Folder 10)
    - Fiese, Marshall J (Folder 10)
    - Francis, John (Folder 10)
    - Lurie, Max B (Folder 10)
    - Freund, Jules (Folder 10)
    - Gabriel, M L (Folder 10)
    - Germuth, Frederick G (Folder 10)
    - Gilchrist Brothers, Ltd. (Folder 10)
    - Brown, K S (Folder 10)
    - Drysdale, G A (Folder 10)
    - Glover, Robert P (Folder 11)
    - Gordon, Irving (Folder 11)
    - Greenman, Lawrence (Folder 11)
    - Hammerman, David J (Folder 11)
    - Hanson, Jean (Folder 11)
    - Hare, Robert (Folder 11)
    - Robertson, O H (Folder 11)
    - Hatch, Milford H (Folder 11)
    - Degenshein, George A (Folder 11)
    - Carlile (Folder 11)
    - Hurwitz, Alfred (Folder 11)
    - Hutchins, Lee M (Folder 11)
    - Institute for Medical Research (Folder 11)
      - Kuala Lumpur (Folder 11)
    - Kabat, Elvin A (Folder 11)
    - Kraljevic, R (Folder 11)
    - Filer, L J., Jr. (Folder 11)
    - Liddle, Gunilla (Folder 11)
    - MacNeily, Mal (Folder 12)
    - Flinn, Waldo R (Folder 12)
    - Maxwell, Ian (Folder 12)
    - Meixner, Margaret D (Folder 12)
    - Melnick, Joseph L (Folder 12)
    - Meyerson, Jean (Folder 12)
    - Behrman, Stanley J (Folder 12)
    - Morgan, Councilman (Folder 12)
    - Muhlethaler, K (Folder 12)
    - Kessler, Stanley (Folder 12)
    - Neilley, Margaret (Folder 12)
    - Oliver, Jean B (Folder 12)
    - Opie, Eugene L (Folder 12)
    - Pappenheimer, A M (Folder 12)
    - Pentimalli, Francesco (Folder 12)
    - Pillemer, Louis (Folder 12)
    - Porter, J R (Folder 13)
    - Porter, Keith R (Folder 13)
    - Ribeiro, L P (Folder 13)
    - Rogers, Edgar Stanfield (Folder 13)
    - Rosenthal, Sol Roy (Folder 13)
    - Russell, Paul S (Folder 13)
    - Samter, Max (Folder 13)
    - Sanders, Murray (Folder 13)
    - Schlesinger, R Walter (Folder 13)
    - Skeggs, Leonard T (Folder 13)
    - Smith, Kenneth (Folder 13)
    - Sherman, William B (Folder 14)
    - West African Council for Medical Research (Folder 14)
    - MacNamara, F N (Folder 14)
    - Thompson, Harlan B (Folder 14)
    - Tsukada, Hideyuki (Folder 14)
    - Owings, A Frank (Folder 14)
    - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission (Folder 14)
    - Weiss, Jules M (Folder 14)
    - Whipple, George H (Folder 14)
    - Whitaker, D (Folder 14)
    - White, Robert G (Folder 14)
    - Yoffey, J M (Folder 14)
    - Angevine, D Murray (Folder 14)
    - Basford, G.M., Co. (Folder 15)
    - Bailey, Richard H (Folder 15)
    - U.S. Army, 204th General Hospital (Guam) (Folder 15)
    - Black, L M (Folder 15)
    - Bodan, David (Folder 15)
    - CIBA Pharmaceutical Products (Folder 15)
    - Daubresse, E (Folder 15)
    - Day, P L (Folder 15)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 15)
    - Dukes, H H (Folder 15)
    - Dunklin, Edward W (Folder 15)
    - Ezeyza, S (Folder 15)
    - Faber, Harold K (Folder 16)
    - Fieschi, Aminta (Folder 16)
    - Astaldi, Giovanni (Folder 16)
    - Freygang, Dorothea (Folder 16)
    - Gasser, H S (Folder 16)
    - Gotthoffer, N R (Folder 16)
    - Grayslake Gelatin Co. (Folder 16)
    - Gurevitch, A D (Folder 16)
    - Heidelberger, Michael (Folder 16)
    - Hoagland, Charles L (Folder 16)
    - Horsfall, Frank L., Jr. (Folder 16)
    - Kabat, Elvin A (Folder 16)
    - Kestler, O C (Folder 16)
    - Klissiunis, Nikolaos (Folder 16)
    - Wulf, Beatrice (Folder 17)
    - Pauling, Linus (Folder 17)
    - Osterhout, W J V (Folder 17)
    - Latarjet, Raymond (Folder 17)
    - Weigand, C G (Folder 17)
    - Mulliken, R S (Folder 17)
    - Ruzicka, L (Folder 17)
    - Mooser, H (Folder 17)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (Folder 17)
    - Van Riper, Hart E (Folder 17)
    - Berg, Roland H (Folder 17)
    - Flinn, Waldo R (Folder 17)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 17)
    - Eagle, Harry (Folder 17)
    - Oxford University Press (Folder 17)
    - Hollis, G T (Folder 17)
    - Peripad Laboratories, Inc. (Folder 18)
    - Burns, Wayne, Jr. (Folder 18)
    - Ruskin, S L (Folder 18)
    - Schroeder, Henry A (Folder 18)
    - Snyder, J C (Folder 18)
    - Calhoun, Helen (Folder 18)
    - Squibb, E.R. & Sons (Folder 18)
    - Farley, A E (Folder 18)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 18)
    - Stewart, M J (Folder 19)
    - This Month in American Medicine (Folder 19)
    - Jensen, Karl E (Folder 19)
    - Thomas, Arthur W (Folder 19)
    - Moch, Royce (Folder 19)
    - U.S. Dept. of State (Folder 19)
    - Cannon, Frank A (Folder 19)
    - U.S. War Dept. (Folder 19)
    - Wetherhold, Frances (Folder 19)
    - Year Book Publishers, Inc. (Folder 19)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 20)
    - Science Service (Folder 20)
    - Davis, Watson (Folder 20)
    - Loveland, E R (Folder 21)
    - Campbell, Editha C (Folder 21)
    - Hallamore, W H (Folder 21)
    - Hunt, H Lyons (Folder 21)
    - Cox, Warren M., Jr. (Folder 21)
    - Stebbins, Frances F (Folder 21)
    - Flexner, Simon (Folder 22)
    - Hess, Sara Straus (Folder 22)
    - Robert, Alfred L (Folder 22)
    - Abbott Laboratories (Folder 23)
    - Lemberger, Helene (Folder 23)
    - Albritton, Errett C (Folder 23)
    - American National Red Cross (Folder 23)
    - Marley, Faye (Folder 23)
    - Powers, Edwin H (Folder 23)
    - American Type Culture Collection (Folder 23)
    - Vera, Harriette D (Folder 23)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 23)
    - Austrian, Robert (Folder 23)
    - Biggs, Rosemary (Folder 23)
    - Popjak, G (Folder 23)
    - British Medical Bulletin (Folder 23)
    - Butterworth's Medical Publications (Folder 24)
    - Burgess, J K (Folder 24)
    - Dunham, Margaret B (Folder 24)
    - Pearce, Louise (Folder 24)
    - Cameron, Hamilton (Folder 24)
    - Cardini, Carlos E (Folder 24)
    - Chase, Merrill W (Folder 24)
    - Sloan, Ralph E (Folder 24)
    - Children's Fund of Mich. (Folder 24)
    - Churchill, J & A., Ltd. (Folder 24)
    - Knightley, A S (Folder 24)
    - Cole, William H (Folder 24)
    - Comar, C L (Folder 24)
    - Dole, Vincent (Folder 24)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 24)
    - Eagle, Harry (Folder 24)
    - Faber, H K (Folder 24)
    - Fischel, Edward E (Folder 24)
    - Florey, Sir Howard (Folder 25)
    - Furth, Jacob (Folder 25)
    - Gitlin, David (Folder 25)
    - Goldblatt, Harry (Folder 25)
    - Hudack, Stephen S (Folder 25)
    - Grant, Madeleine P (Folder 25)
    - Greiff, Donald (Folder 25)
    - Hughes, Grace K (Folder 25)
    - Gasser, Herbert S (Folder 25)
    - Goto, M (Folder 26)
    - Japlan Medical Congress (14th) (Folder 26)
    - Jolles, B (Folder 26)
    - Kempf, J Emerson (Folder 26)
    - Kumabe, Hideo (Folder 26)
    - LeMaistre, Charles A (Folder 26)
    - Lewis, Warren H (Folder 26)
    - University of Buenos Aires. (Folder 26)
    - Loeb, Robert F (Folder 26)
    - Linton, Mrs. Mabel B (Folder 26)
    - Macy, Josiah, Jr., Foundation (Folder 26)
    - Medical Abstracts (Folder 26)
    - Barnes, James D (Folder 26)
    - Rivers, Thomas M (Folder 26)
    - Mirick, George S (Folder 26)
    - Murray, Margaret R (Folder 26)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (Folder 26)
    - Weaver, H M (Folder 26)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 26)
    - Osimani, J J (Folder 27)
    - Parker, Raymond C (Folder 27)
    - Goldstein, M N (Folder 27)
    - Payzin, S (Folder 27)
    - Pitzman, Marsh (Folder 27)
    - Quinlivan, James J (Folder 28)
    - Shorr, Ephraim (Folder 28)
    - Raaschou, Flemming (Folder 28)
    - Roberts, K B (Folder 28)
    - Rudra, M N (Folder 28)
    - Sanders, Murray (Folder 28)
    - Sanyal, S N (Folder 28)
    - Sellers, Alvin L (Folder 28)
    - 7th All India Obstetric and Gynaecological Congress (Folder 28)
    - Das, Probodh (Folder 28)
    - Shute, Evan V (Folder 28)
    - Shwartzman, Gregory (Folder 28)
    - Skoryna, Stanley C (Folder 28)
    - Smith, Gertrude C (Folder 28)
    - Snyder, John C (Folder 29)
    - Lea & Febiger (Folder 29)
    - Sobin, Sidney S (Folder 29)
    - Stamler, Jeremiah (Folder 29)
    - Stevens, Kingsley M (Folder 29)
    - Stewart, Florence M (Folder 29)
    - Dubos, Rene J (Folder 29)
    - Syverton, Jerome T (Folder 29)
    - Tepperman, J (Folder 29)
    - Thimann, Kenneth V (Folder 29)
    - Ray, Tim (Folder 29)
    - Upjohn Co. (Folder 29)
    - Voight, Edwin F (Folder 29)
    - Whelean, Mary Ann (Folder 29)
    - Wiener, Alexander S (Folder 29)
    - Wood, W Barry, Jr. (Folder 29)
    - Woolley, D W (Folder 29)
    - Academie Polonaise Des Sciences et Des Lettres (Folder 30)
    - Atlas, Mrs. Walter (Folder 30)
    - Barrera, Francisco (Folder 30)
    - Bacteriological Research (Folder 30)
    - Cohen, B (Folder 30)
    - Balcazar, Jorge (Folder 30)
    - Barnett, H L (Folder 30)
    - Barrett, Eric (Folder 30)
    - Batson, H C (Folder 30)
    - Black, L M (Folder 30)
    - Bloch, Hubert (Folder 30)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory (Folder 30)
    - MacCorkindale, Mrs. M (Folder 30)
    - Broadbent, Margaret (Folder 30)
    - Cohen, Seymour S (Folder 31)
    - Demko, Vladimir (Folder 31)
    - Dock, William (Folder 31)
    - Eagle, Harry (Folder 31)
    - Experientia (Folder 31)
    - Aellen, Ivonne (Folder 31)
    - Freund, Jules (Folder 31)
    - Friedman, Meyer (Folder 32)
    - Hechter, Oscar (Folder 32)
    - Heidelberger, Michael (Folder 32)
    - Howe, Howard A (Folder 32)
    - Janeway, Charles A (Folder 32)
    - Johnson, Robert E (Folder 32)